<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 3.1.1.50 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://pad.asp-software.org</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>DRK Open Source Software</Company_Name>
		<Address_1>www.drk.com.ar</Address_1>
		<Address_2>blog.drk.com.ar</Address_2>
		<City_Town>Ciudad de Buenos Aires</City_Town>
		<State_Province>Buenos Aires</State_Province>
		<Zip_Postal_Code />
		<Country>Argentina</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Leandro H.</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Fernández</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>drkbugs@gmail.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Leandro H.</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Fernández</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>drkbugs@gmail.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>drkbugs@gmail.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>drkbugs@gmail.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>drkbugs@gmail.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone />
			<Support_Phone />
			<General_Phone />
			<Fax_Phone />
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>Daphne</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>2.03</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>07</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>05</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2014</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win7 x32,Win7 x64,WinServer,WinVista,WinVista x64,WinXP</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English,Arabic,Chinese,French,German,Italian,Japanese,Polish,Portuguese,Russian,Spanish,Swedish</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info>Process owner column, Process I/O read/write columns, Logging facility for process events, Per process detailed I/O information, Major bug fixed: Get process environment information, Major bug fixed: CPU usage not showing if Daphne main window was hidden, Improved web update checking</Program_Change_Info>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>System Utilities::Automation Tools</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements />
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>7073280</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>6907</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>6.75</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count />
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>task manager, process list, close several window, replace, remember window position, hack GUI, validate MD5, validate SHA1, kill process by name, </Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Task manager replacement for Windows (GPL)</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Task manager replacement for Windows with high detail data and automation (GPL)</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Task manager replacement for Windows. Detailed information about process and system state. Automation for killing/closing programs. Command line tool and Windows explorer integration. GUI hacking tools. Drag and drop tool. (GNU GPL)</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Task manager replacement for Windows. Detailed information about process and system state. Automation for killing/closing programs. Command line tool and Windows explorer integration. Drag and drop tool for location process by window, or modifying windows properties. Lock process affinity mask or window size and position. Process hierarchy (GNU GPL)</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Task manager replacement for Windows. Detailed information about process and system state. Automation for killing/closing programs. Command line tool and Windows explorer integration. Drag and drop tool for location process by window, or modifying windows properties. Lock process affinity mask or window size and position. Process hierarchy (GNU GPL):
Resources information
Comprehensive process list
Find/kill the process which owns a given window
Find the window in the process windows tree
Hide window and remove application from task bar
Set or remove always on top property
Change window size using numbers (i.e. 640x480)
Save window position and size and restore when the process is started
Item highlighting with colors for custom, system and high CPU-consumption processes.
Quick search-as-you-type find by process name when sorted by Process column
Schedule process kill for later
Create a trap
Change processor affinity mask and optionally trap this configuration
Copy process name, PID, path, MD5 or SHA1 to clipboard
Open containing folder
Full command line
Parent process and user
Startup timestamp
Kernel and user time
Show and handle minimum and maximum working set size
Send a window message (i.e. WM_ACTIVATE) with lParam and wParam values
Thread list with priority and CPU time
Loaded modules
Environment variables
I/O information
Kill all process by matching name
Close windows by matching title
Schedule popup message
Schedule system shutdown
Control inspector window for revealing hidden passwords and other control information
Copy process list to clipboard
Windows 7 God Mode and Problem steps recorder
Traps apply to any process, when its startup is detected.
Notify creation, Kill, Hide the application, Keep window position and size
User-defined menu items for killing a process list when activated
Four user-defined command lines to be executed by global shortcut
Windows explorer contextual menu integration</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
		<Spanish>
			<Keywords>administrador de tareas, lista de procesos, cerrar varias ventanas, reemplazo, recordar posición y tamaño de ventana, depurar procesos, validar MD5, validar SHA1, terminar procesos por nombre</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Reemplaza administrador de tareas de Windows</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Reemplaza administrador de tareas de Windows con interfaz mejorada (GPL)</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Reemplaza administrador de tareas de Windows con interfaz mejorada, integración con Windows explorer, línea de comandos, automatización, herramienta drag-and-drop, funciones de hacking, accesos directos configurables (GNU GPL)</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Reemplaza administrador de tareas de Windows con interfaz mejorada, integración con Windows explorer, línea de comandos, automatización, herramienta drag-and-drop, funciones de hacking, accesos directos configurables. Ícono arrastable para ubicar un procesos o cerrarlo. Trampas para mantener posición y tamaño de una ventana, y otras propiedades. Árbol de procesos. Agendado de mensajes emergentes o apagado del equipo. (GNU GPL)</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Reemplaza administrador de tareas de Windows con interfaz mejorada, integración con Windows explorer, línea de comandos, automatización, herramienta drag-and-drop, funciones de hacking, accesos directos configurables (GNU GPL) 

Información de recursos
Lista de procesos detallada
Ubicar/terminar el procesos dueño de una ventana
Ubicar una ventana en el árbol de ventanas del proceso
Activar/desactivar la propiedad "Primer plano" de una ventana
Establecer el tamaño de una ventana ingresando un número (ej. 640x480)
Ocultar por completo una aplicación mientras sigue corriendo
Recordar la posición y tamaño de cualquier ventana
Resaltado ajustable de procesos
Agendado de mensajes emergentes, finalización de procesos, o apagado del equipo
Trampas que ejecutan acciones sobre los procesos durante su inicio
Copiar al portapapeles el nombre, ruta completa, PID, hash Md5 o SHA1 de un proceso
Ubicar la carpeta que contiene el ejecutable
Árbol de procesos
Propiedades de una proceso muestra: nombre y PID del padre, tipo de ejecutable, usuario propietario, módulos, variables de entorno, árbol de ventanas e información de E/S.
Soporte para la base de datos de procesos de DRK para la búsqueda y el aporte de información.
Maneja prioridad y máscara de afinidad de CPUs del proceso.
Trampas: se puede enstablecer trampas para aplicar ciertos cambios a procesos en el momento en que comienzan a ejecutarse.
Matar todos por nombre: Elimina todos los procesos con un nombre determinado.
Menú matar: Menú configurable, cada ítem tiene una lista de procesos que será eliminada cuando se active dicho ítem.
Inspector de controles para revelar contraseñas ocultas.
Mira arrastrable para matar, poner transparencia, habilitar controles y poner ventanas en primer plano.
Agregar o quitar programas es una lista de las aplicaciones instaladas similar a la que viene con el sistema operativo, pero más rápida.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</Spanish>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne.php</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne.php</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://drk.com.ar/daphne/ScreenShot_1_201.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne/Daphne.png</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne/Daphne.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne/Daphne_setup_x86.msi</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne/Daphne_setup_x64.msi</Secondary_Download_URL>
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>Daphne -- Windows task manager replacement
Copyright (C) 2005,2014  Leandro H. Fernández

http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne.php

Buenos Aires, Argentina

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 59 Temple Place, Suite 330, Boston, MA  02111-1307  USA

NOTE: You will find the full license terms in COPYING.txt file.

Daphne anonymous statistical-data collection module collects Daphne usage-data 
and sends it to the open statistical database on-line: 
http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne-open-statistics-report.php

Daphne will under no circumstances collect personal data or information about
other software installed on the computer. You can read more about this: 
http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne-anonymous-statistics.php

By installing and/or using Daphne you agree to this anonymous usage-data
collection.</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>Daphne -- Windows task manager replacement
Copyright (C) 2005,2014  Leandro H. Fernández

http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne.php

Buenos Aires, Argentina

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 59 Temple Place, Suite 330, Boston, MA  02111-1307  USA

NOTE: You will find the full license terms in COPYING.txt file.

Daphne anonymous statistical-data collection module collects Daphne usage-data 
and sends it to the open statistical database on-line: 
http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne-open-statistics-report.php

Daphne will under no circumstances collect personal data or information about
other software installed on the computer. You can read more about this: 
http://www.drk.com.ar/daphne-anonymous-statistics.php

By installing and/or using Daphne you agree to this anonymous usage-data
collection.</EULA>
	</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
